Register of the Alfred Kohlberg papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence and Subject File, 1944-1960 (Boxes 1-207)
  - McKinnon, Harold R.
  - McLain, Charles Albert
  - McLeod, Scott
  - McManus, Robert Cruise
  - McSorley, Joseph
  - McWilliam, Carey
  - Meany, George
  - Meet the Press
  - Meetings attended by Kohlberg
  - Melish, John Howard
  - Menefee, Selden C.
  - Meng, Chih
  - Menjou, Adolph
  - Menon, V. K. Krishna
  - Menshikov, Mikhail
  - Menuhin, Yehudi
  - Merwin, Davis
  - Merwin, Wallace C.
  - Mesones, Pedro de
  - Methodists, 2 folders
  - Metropolitan Nicolai
  - Metropolitan Opera (Box 126)
  - Mexico
  - Meyer, Mrs. Eugene
  - Meyer, Frank S.
  - Meyner, Robert B.
  - Mezerik, A. G.
  - Middleton, Drew
  - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw
  - Mikoyan, Anastas Ivanovich
  - Miller, Arthur
  - Miller, Horace Sherman
  - Miller, Merle
  - Miller, Paul and Marion
  - Millikan, Max F.; Millikan and Rostow
  - Millis, Walter
  - Mills, Henry E.
  - Mills College
  - Milton, Paul R.
  - Milwaukee Journal
  - Mindszenty, Joseph, Cardinal
  - Minute Women
  - Mirror. New York Daily Mirror [See also: Ruth Alexander, Lee Mortimer, Drew Pearson, Victor Riesel], 3 folders
  - Mission Board
  - Missionary
  - Missionary letters about communism
  - Missionary magazine, The Far East
  - Modus vivendi
  - Moffett
  - Molotov, V. M.
  - Monroe Doctrine
  - Montgomery, Robert
  - Montgomery, Field Marshall Viscount (Box 127)
  - Monthly Review
  - Montreal Star
  - Moody, Lucian B., 3 folders
  - Moos, Malcolm
  - Moraes, Frank
  - Moral Rearmament
  - Moreell, Ben
  - Morgenthau, Hans, 2 folders
  - Morley, Felix
  - Mormons
  - Morris, Newbold
  - Morris, Robert, 3 folders
  - Morrison, Herbert
  - Morros, Boris
  - Morse, Wayne, 2 folders
  - Mortimer, Lee
  - Mosely, Philip
  - Moss, Anna Lee
  - Mount Holyoke
  - Mow, General P. T.
  - Mowrer, Edgar Ansel, 2 folders
  - Moy, Ernest K. (Box 128)
  - Muir, James
  - Muir, Jean
  - Mullendore, W. C.
  - Mumford, Lewis
  - Mundt, Karl E., 3 folders
  - Muson, Lyle H. [See: Bookmailer]
  - Murphy, Robert
  - Murray, Thomas Edward
  - Murrow, Edward R., 2 folders
  - Muste, A. J. [See also: Fellowship of Reconciliation]
  - Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc.
  - Myers, Fred
  - N, miscellaneous
    - 1959
    - 1958
    - 1956-1957
    - 1955
    - 1954
    - 1953
    - 1952
    - 1951
    - 1950
    - 1949
    - 1948
    - 1947
    - 1946
    - 1945-1951 (Box 129)
    - to 1945
  - Naminow, Djab [See: Kalmuk]
  - Narcotics
  - Nash, Ernest T.
  - Nash, Philleo
  - Nash, Vernon
  - Nasser, Gamal Abdel
  - The Nation, 2 folders
  - Nation's Business, 2 folders
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP)
  - National Association of Manufacturers
  - National Broadcasting Company
  - National Catholic Welfare Conference
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 130)
  - National Council for American Education, 2 folders
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc.
  - National Council of Churches of Christ, 2 folders
  - National Council of Jewish Women
  - National Council of Women
  - National Council on Asian Affairs
  - National Economic Council, 2 folders
  - National Educational Program [See also: Harding College]
  - National Exchange Clubs, 1950
  - National Foreign Trade Council, Inc. (Box 131)
  - National Geographic Society
  - National Guardian
  - National Industrial Council
  - National Institute of Social Relations, Inc.
  - National Issues Committee
  - National Jewish Hospital
  - National Jewish Post
  - National Lawyer's Guild
  - National Layman's Council, Church League of America, 2 folders
  - National News-Letter, edited by S. King-Hall, 3 folders
  - National Planning Association
  - National Republic
  - National Republican Club, 2 folders
  - National Review, 1955-1959; 6 folders (Box 132)
  - National Sharecroppers Fund
  - National Student Association
  - Navy Department, United States
  - Navy Intelligence School, Reading Log
  - Nearing, Scott
  - Needham, Joseph
  - Nehru, Jawaharlal
  - Nelson, Donald
  - Nelson, Frederic
  - The Network
  - Neuberger, Richard L. (Box 133)
  - Neuman, William F.
  - Nevins, Allan
  - New Bedford Standard Times, 1952-1959; 6 folders
  - New Century Publishers
  - New China News Agency
  - New Council of American Business [See: Samuel Rubin]
  - The New Leader
    - 1951-1959, 7 folders
    - 1945-1949, 8 folders (Box 134)
  - New Masses
  - The New Republic, 2 folders
  - New School
  - New Statesman and Nation
  - New Times
  - New World Review
  - New York
  - New York banks
  - New York City Council (Box 135)
  - New York Daily News, 1951-1959; 4 folders
  - New York Public Library
  - New York School of Psychology
  - New York State
  - New York University
  - The New Yorker
  - New Zealand
  - Newman, Joseph
  - Newman, Rabbi Louis I.
  - News Behind the News, published by the National Federation of Christian Laymen
  - Newsday
  - Newsletter, The, published in cooperation with "Possev"
  - Newsweek
    - 1948-1959, 6 folders
    - 1945-1947, 2 folders (Box 136)
  - Neylan, John Francis
  - Nichols, C. Ralph, Mr. and Mrs
  - Nicolai, Metropolitan [See: Metropolitan Nicolai]
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold
  - Niles, David K.
  - Nine Power Treaty
  - Nisselson, Michael
  - Nitze, Paul Henry
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1948-1959; 8 folders
  - Nobel Prize
  - Noble, Harold J.
  - Nomura, Kichisaburo
  - Norman, E. Herbert
  - North, Robert C. (Box 137)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO)
  - NTS (National Alliance of Russian Solidarists), 2 folders
  - Nunez-Portuondo, Emilio [See also: Cuba]
  - Nutting, Anthony
  - O, miscellaneous
    - 1957-
    - 1953-1956
    - 1950-1952
    - -1949
    - 1946-1951
  - Oakes, John B.
  - Oakland Tribune
  - O'Conor, Herbert R., 2 folders
  - Odlum, Floyd
  - O'Donnel, John, 2 folders
  - Office of War Information
  - O'Gara, Cuthbert M., Bishop of Yuanling, Hunan Province, China
  - O'Hara, Barratt
  - Ohio Subversive Control Law, 1953 August
  - "Oil" letters
  - O'Konski, Alvin E. (Box 138)
  - Oliver, Revilo Pendleton
  - Oliver, Sherling
  - Olympic Games
  - Open Door Policy
  - Operation Brotherhood
  - Operations Research Office
  - Oppenheimer, Frank
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert
  - Orr, Lord Boyd
  - Osborn, Gardner, 2 folders
  - Otterbourg, Steindler, Houston and Rosen
  - Overseas News Agency
  - Overseas Press Club
  - Overstreet, Harry
  - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 2 folders
  - P, miscellaneous
    - 1958-1959
    - 1957
    - 1956
    - 1955
    - 1954 July-December
    - 1954 January-June
    - 1953 July-December
    - 1953 January-June (Box 139)
    - 1952 July-December
    - 1952 January-June
    - 1951
    - 1950
    - 1949
    - 1948
    - 1947
    - 1946-1947
    - 1945-1951
    - to 1945 December 31
  - Pacific Publishing Foundation, Inc.
  - Pacific Shipper, Inc.
  - Padev, Michael A.
  - Paix et Liberté (France)
  - Pakistan
  - Pan, Stephen C. Y.
  - Pan Pacific Children Center
  - Pande, Gunnar A.
  - Pandit, Mme Vijaya L.
  - Panikkar, K. M.
  - Panuch, J. Anthony
  - Parent Teacher's Association
  - Parlin, Charles C.
  - Parry, Albert
  - Parsons, J. Graham
  - The Passing Caravan, 2 folders
  - Pasternak, Boris (Box 140)
  - Pasvolksi, Dr.
  - Pathfinder Magazine
  - Patrick Henry League, The
  - Patterson, Ellis E.
  - Patterson, Robert P., 2 folders
  - Pauker, Ana
  - Pauling, Linus
  - Payne, Robert
  - "Peace" meeting
  - Peace Publications Fund
  - Peale, Norman Vincent
  - Pearl Harbor
  - Pearson, Drew, 4 folders
  - Pearson, Lester
  - Peekskill, 1949 September
  - Peffer, Nathaniel, 2 folders
  - Pegler, Westbrook
  - Pegler, Westbrook, 3 folders (Box 141)
  - Peking Peace Meeting
  - Peking Review
  - Pell, Herbert
  - Penemunde
  - Penha, Armando
  - Pentagon Case [See also: Col. Victor J. Fox]
  - People to People Program
  - Peoples China
  - Pepper, Claude
  - Peress, Irving
  - Perlo, Victor
  - Perry, Ralph Barton
  - Peterman, Ivan H.
  - Peters, Harvey
  - Peterson, A. D. C.
  - Peterson, W. Fairfield, 2 folders
  - Petrov, Vladimir
  - Peurifoy, John E.
  - Pew, J. Howard
  - Philadelphia
  - Philbrick, Herbert A.
  - Philippines
  - Philipps, Cabell
  - Phillips, J. C. [See also: American Legion]
  - Phillips, Nathaniel
  - Phillips, Neill (Box 142)
  - Picasso, Pablo
  - Pike, James A.
  - Pirnie, W. Bruce
  - Plain Talk
    - 1948-1949
    - 1946-1947
    - 1946-1950
  - "A Platform in Search of a Party," A. Kohlberg, 1959
  - Platforms, political, 2 folders
  - Plecan, Theodore P., Disillusionment of a Radical
  - PM, 3 folders
  - PM, 3 folders (Box 143)
  - Point Four
  - Poland
  - Poling, Daniel A., 2 folders
  - Polish affairs, 2 folders
  - Polish aid
  - Polish-American Congress
  - Political action committee, 2 folders
  - Political Affairs
  - The Political Quarterly
  - Pool, Rabbi David de Sola
  - The Pope (Pius XII)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham
  - Population Reference Bureau
  - Porter, Charles O. (Box 144)
  - Porter, Ruth
  - Portugal
  - Possony, Stefan T.
  - Post. The New York Post and James Wechsler, 1951-1958; 4 folders
  - Potsdam
  - Potter, John
  - "Potter of Nuzi" letters
  - Poulson, Norris
  - Pound, Roscoe
  - Powell, Adam Clayton
  - Powell, John W. (Bill), China Weekly Review, 2 folders
  - Powell, Paulus P.
  - POWs
  - Praeger (Publications)
  - Pratt, Sir John
  - Pravda. Excerpts, 1948-1952; 2 folders
  - Pregel, Boris
  - Preparedness Committee (U.S. Senate Subcommittee)
  - Presbyterians, 2 folders (Box 145)
  - Price, Frank Wilson
  - Price, Harry B.
  - Price, Mildred
  - Price, Theodore
  - Princeton University [See also: H. W. Dodds]
  - Pro-American
  - Problems of Communism
  - Production
  - Prognostications - Alfred Kohlberg
  - Progressive
  - Propaganda
  - Prophecy of elections, 1954
  - Protect America League, Inc., Neil E. Wetterman, President
  - The Protestant
  - Public Action, Inc.
  - Public Affairs Committee
  - Public Affairs Pamphlets
  - Public library
  - Puerto Rico
  - Puleston, W. D.
  - Q, miscellaneous
  - Queen Elizabeth (Queen Elizabeth II)
  - Quemoy
  - Quotations, 2 folders
  - R, miscellaneous
    - 1958-1959
    - 1957
    - 1956
    - 1955
    - 1954
    - 1953 (Box 146)
    - 1952
    - 1951
    - 1950
    - 1949
    - 1948
    - 1947
    - 1946
    - to 1945 December 31
    - R*
  - Rabi, I. I.
  - Rabinowitch, Eugene
  - Radford, Arthur W.
  - Radio Free Asia
  - Rajchman, Ludwig
  - Rakosi, Matyas
  - Rampart
  - Rand, Christopher
  - Randall Commission (Commission on Foreign Economic Policy)
  - Rankin, Karl
  - Rascoe, Burton, 2 folders
  - Ravenholt, Albert
  - Ray, Edwin O'Miles
  - Ray, J. Franklin
  - Raymond, Jack (Box 147)
  - Reader's Digest, 2 folders
  - Realpolitical Institute
  - Recognition of Red China, 1953-1958; 4 folders
  - Red Dean Hewlett Johnson
  - Reece, Carroll
  - Regnery Company, Henry
  - Regnery Company, Henry (Box 148)
  - Reinhardt, Guenther
  - Reischauer, Edwin O.
  - Report on China, 1949 August; 2 folders
  - The Reporter, 1952-1957; 3 folders
  - Republican Party (United States)
  - Republican National Committee
  - Republican platform, 1952 and 1956; 2 folders
  - Republican State Central Committee, Oregon
  - Research
  - Research Associates
  - Resolution on Middle East
  - Reston, James B.
  - Reuther, Walter
  - Reynolds, Quentin
  - Rhee, Syngman (Box 149)
  - Richards, Ray
  - Richardson, Seth
  - Richardson Foundation
  - Rickenbacker, Edward V.
  - Riencort, Amaury de
  - Rickett, Allyn
  - Riesel, Victor
  - Robertson, Kenneth D., Jr.
  - Robertson, Walter S. [See also: State Department], 4 folders
  - Robeson, Paul
  - Robinson, Jay
  - Robinson, Reid
  - Robinson, Richard D.
  - Rochester University
  - Rockefeller brothers (Nelson, John D., III, Winthrop)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1945-1958; 3 folders
  - Roepke, Wilhelm
  - Rogers, William P.
  - Rohrbaugh, Mrs. (Box 150)
  - Romerstein, Herbert
  - Romulo, Carlos P.
  - Roodkowsky, Nikita D.
  - Roosevelt, Archibald, 1954-1958; 5 folders
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 2 folders
  - Roosevelt, Elliott
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr.
  - Roosevelt, Nicholas
  - Roosevelt, Theodore
  - Root, E. Merrill
  - Roper, Elmo
  - Ropes, E. C.
  - Rorty, James
  - Rosenberg, Anna M.
  - Rosenberg, Ethel and Julius
  - Rosenthal, Morris S.
  - Rosinger, L. K., 2 folders
  - Rossiter, Clinton
  - Rostow, W. W. (Box 151)
  - Roth, Andrew, 3 folders
  - Rovere, Richard
  - Rowe, David Nelson
  - Roy, Ralph L.
  - Royall, Kenneth
  - Rubin, Samuel [See also: UJA]
  - Rugg, Harold
  - Rushmore, Howard
  - Rusk, Dean, 2 folders
  - Russell, Bertrand
  - Russell, George
  - Russell, Lord of Liverpool
  - Russia [See also: U.S.S.R.]
  - Russian Relief, Inc.
  - Russian translator
  - Ryskind, Morrie
  - S, miscellaneous
    - 1959
    - 1958
    - 1957 (Box 152)
    - 1956
    - 1955
    - 1954
    - 1953
    - 1952
    - 1951
    - 1950
    - 1950-1951 (Box 153)
    - 1949
    - 1948
    - 1947
    - 1946
    - 1942-1949
    - to 1945
  - Sachs, Alexander
  - Sack, A. J.
  - St. Laurent, Louis
  - St. Louis Post Dispatch, 2 folders
  - Saionji, Prince Kimikazu
  - Salisbury, Harrison, 2 folders
  - San Antonio newspapers
  - San Francisco Call Bulletin
  - San Francisco Chamber of Commerce
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 2 folders
  - San Francisco Daily People's World, 2 folders
  - Sandburg, Carl
  - Santo, John
  - Sapiro, Aaron
  - Sarah Lawrence College (Box 154)
  - Sargent, Aaron M.
  - Sargent, James
  - Sarnoff, David
  - Saroyan, William
  - Sartre, Jean-Paul
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1944-1958; 6 folders
  - Saturday Review of Literature
  - Saunders, John
  - Scandrett, Richard B.
  - Schappes, Morris U.
  - Scherer, Gordon H.
  - Scherer, Marcel (Box 155)
  - Scherman, Harry (Book of the Month Club)
  - Schieber, Habib
  - Schlesinger, Arthur
  - Schmidt, Emerson P.
  - Schnitzer, George C.
  - Schools
  - Schuman, Frederick L.
  - Schuman, Julian [See also: John W. Powell]
  - Schwartz, Harry, New York Times
  - Schwarz, Fred C., 3 folders
  - Scott, Charles Ernest
  - Scratch, Walter L.
  - Seale, Lewis J.
  - Searchlight
  - Searls, Fred
  - Sears, Louis Martin
  - Southeast Asia Treaty Organization (SEATO)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box 156)
  - Seldes, George
  - Seligman, Eustace
  - Selvage, James P.
  - Seminars, 1957
  - Senate, United States
  - Senate, United States [See: Foreign Aid Study]
  - Senators. Letter to newspapers of states represented by them, 1949
  - Senter, David
  - Sergio, Lisa
  - Service, John Stewart
  - Serwer, Harry
  - Sevareid, Eric
  - Seversky, Alexander P. de
  - Seymour, Lawrence D.
  - Seymour, Whitney North
  - Sforza, Cour Johnson
  - Shafer, Paul W.
  - Shahn, Ben
  - Shanahan, Father Cormac
  - Shanghai Evening Post and Mercury
  - Shanks Village
  - Shapiro, Nathan
    - 1955-1959, 2 folders
    - 1946-1954, 7 folders (Box 157)
  - Shapley, Harlow
  - Shaw, Bruno
  - Sheil, Bishop Bernard J.
  - Shen Chang-huan, secretary to the Generalissimo
  - Sherrod, Robert Lee
  - Shipler, Guy Emery
  - Shirer, William L.
  - Short, Irving, 2 folders (Box 158)
  - Shotwell, James T.
  - Shriver, J. Nicholas, 2 folders
  - Shumlin, Herman
  - Shuster, George N.
  - Siberia, Report on, 1952 January
  - Sie Cheou-Kang, H. E.
  - The Sign
  - Sih, Paul K. T.
  - Silver, Rabbi Abba Hillel
  - Silvermaster, Nathan Gregory
  - Simms, William Philip, 2 folders
  - Simpson, Thacher and Bartlett
  - Sinatra, Frank
  - Singer, Kurt
  - Singh, J. J.
  - Sino-American Amity, Inc., 1952-1958; 2 folders
  - Sino-Russian Pact, August 25, 1945 [See: Treaties]
  - Sino-U.S. Treaty [See: Treaties]
  - Slavery
  - Slessor, John
  - Smedley, Agnes, 2 folders
  - Smedley-Stein spy case, 1949
  - Smith, Gerald L. K. (Box 159)
  - Smith, H. Alexander, 2 folders
  - Smith, Lawrence, 2 folders
  - Smith, Leigh
  - Smith, Margaret Chase
  - Smith, Paul C.
  - Smith, Sterling L.
  - Smith, Walter Bedell
  - Smoot, Dan
    - 1959
    - 1958
    - Dan Smoot Speaks
      - 1957
      - 1956
      - 1955
  - Snow, Edgar
  - Sobell, Morton (Box 160)
  - Soble family
  - Socialists - United States
  - Society for the Prevention of World War II
  - Sockman, Ralph W.
  - Soderbom, George
  - Sokolsky, George, 1944-1960; 6 folders
  - Sooneborn, Rudolf G.
  - Sons of the American Revolution
  - Soong, T. V., 2 folders
  - Souers, Sidney W.
  - Sourwine, Jay
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare
  - Southern States Industrial Council (Box 161)
  - Southern Weekly
  - Souvarine, Boris
  - Soviet escapees. Issues of The Challenge, Bulletin of the Association of Political Prisoners of Soviet Labor Camps, Inc.
  - Soviet Total War
  - Spadea Syndicate, Inc.
  - Spain
  - Spangler, Fred T.
  - Spanish gold
  - Sparkman, John
  - Speech materials
  - Speeches - Alfred Kohlberg
    Includes April 1957, Miami Beach, Association of American Physicians and Surgeons.
  - Spellman, Francis Cardinal, 2 folders
  - Spiritual Mobilization (Box 162)
  - Sproul, Robert G., 2 folders
  - SPX Research Associates (Col. Tom R. Hutton)
  - Spies
  - Spy case folder
  - Staley, Eugene
  - Stalin, Joseph
  - Standley, William H.
  - Stanford University
  - Star. New York Star, 2 folders
  - Stassen, Harold E., 2 folders
  - State, United States Department of
    - 1958-1960, 2 folders
    - 1955-1956 (Box 163)
    - 1953-1954
    - 1951-1952
    - Through 1950
    - *1950-1953
    - Through *1949
    - 1938- (Box 164)
      Cordell Hull, Stanley Hornbeck, Maxwell Hamilton, and others.
    - Pamphlets and bulletins, 1955-1956
    - Statement to Senate Appropriations Committee
  - Steel, Johannes
  - "Steel Helmet"
  - Steel production [See also: Production]
  - Steele, A. T.
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur
  - Stein, Gunther
  - Stein, Richard
  - Steinkraus, Herman W.
  - Stephens, Roderick (Committee for Collective Security)
  - Stettinius, E. R.
  - Stevens, Doris
  - Stevens, Helen K.
  - Stevens, Roger L.
  - Stevenson, Adlai E.
    - 1953-1958, 5 folders
    - 1952, 2 folders (Box 165)
  - Stewart, Donald O.
  - Stewart, Maxwell S.
  - Stilwell, Joseph W., 2 folders
  - Stokes, Richard L., 2 folders
  - Stone, I. F.
  - Stone, Walker
  - Stoutenburgh, Paul P.
  - Stowe, Leland, 2 folders
  - Straight, Michael [See also: New Republic], 2 folders
  - Stratemeyer, George E.
  - Stratton, Sally
  - Straus, Donald B.
  - Strauss, Lewis L.
  - Strausz-Hupe, Robert
  - Streibert, Tehodore C. [See: United States Intelligence Agency]
  - Stringfellow, George E.
  - Strohm, John Lewis
  - Strong, Anna Louise
  - Strong, Robert Campbell
  - Struik, Dirk J.
  - Stuart, John Leighton, 2 folders
  - Stuart, Lyle
  - Subersive Activities Control Board, 1950 (Box 166)
  - Suchman, Mrs. Edward
  - Sues, Ilona Ralf
  - Suitors and Suppliants
  - Sukarno, President of Indonesia
  - Sullivan, Mark, 2 folders
  - Sulzberger, C. L., 4 folders
  - Summit conferences
  - Sun. The New York Sun
    - 1948 - 1949 July, 8 folders
    - 1944 - 1948 May, 10 folders (Box 167)
  - Sun Yat-sen, Mme. Statements, 1946 July; 2 folders
  - Superintendent of Documents
  - Supreme Court (Box 168)
  - Suyin, Han
  - Sweezy, Paul M.
  - Swerdloff, Sam
  - Swing, Raymond Gram
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard
  - Symington, W. Stuart
  - Syracuse meeting, 1954 March 11
  - Szilard, Leo
  - T, miscellaneous
    - 1958-1959
    - 1956-1957
    - 1953-1955
    - 1949-1952
    - to 1948
    - *1945-1951
  - The Tablet, 1946-1959; 3 folders
  - The Tablet* (Box 169)
  - Taft, Robert A., 3 folders
  - Taipeh Newsletter
  - Taiping Rebellion [See: CENIS]
  - Taiwan University
  - Talbott, Harold
  - Tang, Peter S. H.
  - Taplinger, Richard
  - Task Force Report: American Strategy and Strength, 1960 June
  - Tax Exempt Foundations, U.S. House Committee on, 2 folders
  - Tax Foundation, Inc.
  - Taylor, Blair
  - Taylor, Floyd
  - Taylor, George E.
  - Taylor, Harold [See also: Sarah Lawrence College] (Box 170)
  - Taylor, Telford
  - Taylor, William H.
  - Tchou, Col. Thomas M.
  - Teacher's College (Columbia University)
  - Teeple, David S.
  - Teheran
  - Teller, Edward
  - Temple University
  - Ten Million
  - Tenney, Jack B., 1945-1954; 5 folders
  - Texas
  - Textor, Robert B.
  - Thayer, Charles W.
  - Theses and statutes of the Third International
  - Thomas, J. Parnell, 2 folders
  - Thomas, Norman
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 2 folders
  - Thorez, Maurice
  - Thorp, Willard
  - Thorpe, Elliott R.
  - Three-Star Extra
  - Thunder Out of China, White and Jacoby
  - Tibet
  - Tillinger, Eugene
  - Time Magazine, 1944-1959; 4 folders (Box 171)
  - Times. New York Times
    - 1959
    - Correspondence
      - 1954-1958, 5 folders
      - 1947-1953, 8 folders (Box 172)
    - Clippings
      - 1957 October - 1960
      - 1955 October - 1957 September, 8 folders (Box 173)
      - 1954 July - 1955 September, 4 folders (Box 174)
      - 1953 April - 1954 June (Box 175)
      - 1951 September - 1953 March (Box 176)
      - 1950 September - 1951 August, 6 folders (Box 177)
      - 1949 November - 1950 August, 5 folders (Box 178)
      - 1949 February-September, 7 folders (Box 179)
      - 1948 August - 1949 January (Box 180)
      - 1947 October - 1948 July (Box 181)
      - 1946 October - 1947 September (Box 182)
      - 1945 December - 1946 September (Box 183)
      - 1945 July-November (Box 184)
      - 1944 - 1945 June (Box 185)
    - Book reviews, 1945-1960; 3 folders (Box 186)
    - Magazine section, 1945-1960; 10 folders
  - Timperley, H. J.
  - Tiro, Hasan M.
  - Tishman, Maurice [folder is empty, April 1991]
  - Tito
  - Tobias, Channing Heggie
  - Today's World, 2 folders
  - Todt, George H.
  - Tokaev, Grigori A.
  - Toledano, Ralph and Norma de, 2 folders (Box 187)
  - Toledano, Vicente Lombardo
  - Tomorrow
  - Tong, Hollington K., 3 folders
  - Topeka, Kansas
  - Toronto, Canada
  - Toronto Globe and Mail
  - Torossian, Vincent
  - Town Hall, Inc., 3 folders
  - Town Journal
  - Toynbee, Arnold J.
  - Trade
  - Trager, Frank N.
  - Treason
  - Treasury, United States Department of (Box 188)
  - Treaties
  - Trevor, John B.
  - Trilling, Diana
  - Trotskyites
  - Trott, Zu
  - True Magazine
  - Trujillo, Rafael L.
  - Truman, Harry S., 1946-1956; 6 folders
  - Truth About Communism, The [See: Rev. Cletus Healy]
  - Tsai, Father Mark
  - Tseu, Augustinius
  - Tsiang, Tingfu F. [See also: Chinese delegation to the United Nations]
  - Tsuru, Shigeto (Box 189)
  - Tugwell, Rexford
  - Turck, Charles J.
  - Turzinski, Cornelius
  - Tydings, Millard
  - U, miscellaneous
    - 1958
    - 1945-1957
    - *1945-1951
  - U Nu
  - Ukraine
  - Ultimatum (U.S. to Japan, November 26, 1941)
  - Un-American Activities, Committee on (U.S. House of Representatives), 4 folders
  - Union of Democratic Control
  - Union Research Service, 2 folders
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics [See also: Russia]
  - Union Theological Seminary
  - Unitarians
  - United American Veterans
  - United Americans Against Communism
  - United China Relief, - 1946 August 19
  - United China Relief (Box 190)
  - United Electrical Workers Union
  - United Kingdom
    - General
    - Newspapers
  - United Mine Workers
  - United Nations agreement, Kohlberg's proposed, 1943
  - United Nations Organization
    - San Francisco Conference, 2 folders
    - Withdrawal
    - UNESCO, 2 folders
    - UNICEF
    - UNRRA, 2 folders
    - United Nations World, 2 folders
  - United Press, 2 folders
  - United Service to China (formerly United China Relief), 4 folders (Box 191)
  - United States Information Agency, 2 folders
  - United States National Students Association
  - U.S.A Magazine, 1955-1959; 5 folders
  - U.S. Mission to the U.N.
  - U.S. News and World Report
    - 1948-1959, 9 folders (Box 192)